My name is Jared Jeffrey. I'm CEO and
founder at HealthKERI. Really excited to
be here at the KERI conference today. We
just did a session on using the VLEI in
healthcare to basically solve the problem
of organizational identity. So with
healthcare organizations, there's really
not a good identifier to help you
understand which organization you're
talking to. So as just a quick example, if
you talk about St. Mary's, well, which St.
Mary's? There's, you know, 17 of them. And
which St. Mary's owned by which
organization? Because several St. Mary's
are owned by the same organization.
Several are owned, you know, by other
organizations. So really what we're trying
to solve here is can we bootstrap rapid
connectivity using KERI and the VLEI?
Yeah, so I think one of the things that I
see maybe differently than the rest of the
world here is that everybody else has kind
of adopted now 25-year-old security
technology, you know, tokens, OAuth,
OAuth, things of that nature that were
really never designed for an ecosystem
that exists here today. So we've kind of
carried this legacy architecture into the
modern world where not only do you have
way more organizations doing connections,
you know, real time, but you also have
things like not just AI internally being
used in LLMs, but agentic AI. So you have
kind of created an entirely new entity
class for connectivity. And I think a lot
of people are still trying to take this
round hole and fill it with the old square
peg of last year's cybersecurity
protocols. So what would the decentralized
identity system lose if all of our work at
HealthKERI had evaporated? Well, I think
the easiest answer is as of today, we put
a ton of code into the open source. So one
of the biggest complaints we heard about
people that didn't want to adopt KERI or
were slow to move into a KERI-based
ecosystem was that KERI was too
complicated and the infrastructure wasn't
there. We recognize that a rising tide
raises all boats. And so we just recently
put into open source a production ready
wallet that can handle KERI identifiers.
We put into open source witnesses and
watcher code as well. Those three
components are three of the five Ws that
are being asked for from the KERI that are
being asked for from the KERI Foundation.
So by putting those into open source,
we're really putting a commitment into
this ecosystem saying we want all of the
parties that are interested in seeing KERI
be successful come to the table and
collaborate with us. So if all of that
went away today, you would lose probably
two years worth of solid work from one of
the best developers, Phil Therheller on
bringing health KERI or KERI at large into
existence. S nicotine nicotine nicotine
nicotine nicotine nicotine nicotine
nicotine nicotine nicotine nicotine nic
nic nic nic nic nic nic nic nic nic nic
nic nic nic Imagine Imagine Imagine
Imagine Imagine Imagine Imagine Imagine